massgenie.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy

**Effective February 2017**

At MassGenie, your privacy is not a game but a serious matter.  This Privacy Notice explains the way we use the information you provide when you register for a MassGenie account.

**Collecting your information**

**Information you provide**

You provide information to us when you access MassGenie, which includes when you register an account, join our mailing lists, commit to a Power Deal, contact us, make a review, or join a contest, loyalty program or any promotion MassGenie has sponsored.  The information you provide may include but are not limited to:

●     Contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address. 

●     Payment information such as your credit card details, and banking and/or payment details 

●     Your shipping information such as names, addresses, and contact numbers for anyone to whom you want the item to be shipped to. 

You may also access MassGenie using a social network (e.g. Facebook, Twitter, Instagram) or other third-party websites.  We may collect your name and other details available from your social network account or third-party website account.

In addition to our Terms & Conditions, you will also be bound by the terms of use and privacy policies of these social networks and third-party websites.

**Information collected by automated means**

When you use MassGenie, we and third-party vendors may collect information via automated means. This includes cookies, Web server logs, Web beacons, JavaScript, and components of our apps. We may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or that you provide to us.

**_What about "cookies"?_**

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and MassGenie does not use cookies to collect personal information. Rather, we use cookies to log you onto the site.

MassGenie may use HTTP cookies, HTML5 cookies, Flash cookies, and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage). You may be notified when you receive certain types of cookies by your browser.  You can also set your browser to restrict or disable certain cookies. 

**_Web server logs and Web Beacons_**

Web server logs may collect information about the device you are using to access MassGenie, its operating system, browser, domain, and other system settings, including the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located; the address of the Web page that referred you to MassGenie; your device’s IP address; and other information about the way you accessed MassGenie.  We may place small electronics tags called Web beacons on our pages and emails to collect information by automated means. They link Web pages to particular Web servers and their cookies. These tags allow you to fully use all features of MassGenie.

**_JavaScript_**

MassGenie and/or third parties may also may send instructions to your device using JavaScript or other computer languages to store or gather the sorts of information described above and other details about your interactions with MassGenie. 

**_SDKs_**

When you install the MassGenie mobile application, we may work with partners and service providers who use mobile “SDKs” or similar code, in order to collect information such as device identifiers, mobile advertising identifiers (e.g., IDFAs and Android Advertising IDs), IP addresses, Internet connection information, as well as details about your device (such as device type), mobile browser or operating system, or about how you interact with our apps or services. A mobile SDK is in effect the mobile app version of a pixel tag or beacon. The SDK is computer code that app developers can include in their apps to enable ads to be shown, data to be collected, and related services to be implemented. We may use this technology, for instance, to analyze how our customers use our applications and make purchases, or to deliver or measure certain advertising through mobile applications and browsers based on information associated with your mobile device. These SDKs (or other, similar mobile applications and code) may collect mobile identifiers or geolocation information, which may be precise, GPS-level information. If you would like to opt out from having ads tailored to you in this way on your mobile device, please go to the “Settings” on your mobile device for directions on how to do so.

**Using Your Information**

The information you have provided as well as the ones we have collected via automated means shall be used to:

●      Process, evaluate, and respond to your requests, inquiries, and applications; 

●      Create, administer, and communicate with you about your account; 

●      Constantly improve your experience as a MassGenie user; 

●      Send you information about MassGenie items and services as well as our Sellers; 

●      Display advertising relevant to you at MassGenie and across the Internet; 

●      Operate, evaluate, and improve MassGenie and our items and services (including to analyze, customize and develop new items and services; perform market research, data analytics, and data enhancement; measure the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing; administer MassGenie; and perform accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation, and collection activities);

●      Verify your identity and protect against fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims, and other liabilities;

●      Comply with applicable laws, regulations, and industry standards and enforce our rights under  MassGenie Terms & Conditions and other policies; and

●      Inform you about updates to MassGenie, this Privacy Notice, our Terms and Conditions, and other policies that may be created in the future.

We use Google Analytics and other third-party Web analytics services to help us analyze how users such as you use MassGenie. These service providers use cookies and other automated technologies to collect information about you when you visit MassGenie. Learn about Google Analytics and its opt-out choices here.

The information we will collect from ad services we use may track your online activities. These third-party ad services may use this information to show you advertisements for MassGenie items and services that are tailored to your individual interests or characteristics and/or based on prior visits to MassGenie. We and third-party vendors may use these cookies together, and may combine them with other data we collect from you, (1) to inform, optimize, and serve ads (including ads based on past visits to MassGenie) and (2) to report on ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services (including how they are related to visits to MassGenie). 

**_Do Not Track_**

Do Not Track is a voluntary program among advertisers giving users the ability to opt out of behavioral targeting and advertising. At this time, MassGenie does respond to “do not track” settings.

**_Sharing your information_**

We may share the information we collect or you provide with our service providers and the merchants who fulfill your orders, affiliates, and joint marketing partners, for any of the purposes set forth in this Privacy Notice. These may include, but are not limited to, service providers that provide hosting services, customer and technical support, marketing, billing, payment, or email services, security, anti-fraud, or other operational support.

We may also share your information when you sign up for a MassGenie account by clicking on an affiliate or referral link (e.g., on a social media site or elsewhere online) served by someone who has identified you as their contact. 

We may share aggregated, anonymized, or de-identified personal information with any third party, without any restriction, including through the use of cookies and other automated technologies.

Subject to applicable law, your personal information may be disclosed if: we are required to do so by law, regulation, court order or legal process; when we believe disclosure would be appropriate in response to governmental or regulatory requests; when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical, financial, or other harm, injury, or loss; in connection with an investigation of unlawful activity; and for fraud detection and prevention.

Any personal information we have about you may be transferred to a buyer or other successor in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (such as in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, dissolution, or liquidation), or take steps in anticipation of such a transaction.

Third parties may collect personal information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use MassGenie.  These may include, but are not limited to, third-party providers of certain embedded content and tools at MassGenie (such as social network plug-ins) who may collect personal information directly from you in connection with your interaction with such content and tools. The use of such information is subject to the third party’s own privacy policies. We are not responsible for such providers’ privacy practices, which are not covered by this Privacy Notice. 

**_Your Options_**

You may choose not to provide information, which might hamper your ability to commit to Power Deals or other present and future features MassGenie may provide.

You may update or modify your personal information by logging into your account.  You may also contact us at [customerservice@massgenie.com](mailto:customerservice@massgenie.com) or by following the steps in our Contact Us page.

You may also unsubscribe from any of our promotional emails by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any MassGenie promotional emails you may receive.

**_Securing your information_**

We strive to protect your information at all costs but we can’t promise that the steps we have undertaken eliminate all possible security risks. When you provide information to us, you do so at your own risk.

You can also ensure protection of your MassGenie account by doing the following:

1.       When creating an account and logging in at MassGenie, use a unique password that has never been used or will be used anywhere else;

2.       Ensure the confidentiality of your login information. Do not share your username or password to anyone, anywhere, anytime;

3.       Access MassGenie only from devices that have an up-to-date operating system and up-to-date security software; and

4.       Immediately notify us of any suspected malicious and/or unauthorized activity by emailing us at [security@massgenie.com](mailto:security@massgenie.com).

These steps do not guarantee ironclad security but will definitely help lower the risk or impact of certain security threats. Visit [http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/computer-security](http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/computer-security) for more information on protecting your security.

**Linking to Other Websites and Online Services**

MassGenie may provide links to other third-party websites and online services, such as merchants or manufacturers of items sold at MassGenie or other third-party service providers that help MassGenie to operate. They may have their own privacy policies, which we strongly suggest you read and review. We are not responsible for the content or use of any third-party websites or services or their privacy or security practices.

**_Updating this Privacy Notice_**

MassGenie may update this Privacy Notice from time to time to adhere to relevant laws and changes in the way we manage our business. We will notify you of any changes that we make, post the updated version on [www.massgenie.com](http://www.massgenie.com/), and show the effective date of such change.
